(Leonard:)for innocent little boys
who just want to be happy?
(Dr Gallo:)Well, I didn't want to say it...
(Leonard:)No, no, say it. Sing it.
(Leonard:)Rent a plane,
write it in the sky.
(Dr Gallo:)Sounds like you're holding on
(Dr Gallo:)to quite a bit of anger
towards her.
(Penny:)Oh, no,
I-I've worked through
a lot of that stuff;
I'm better now.
(Dr Gallo:)Mm. Good for you.
(Leonard:)Do you know she never let me
(Leonard:)celebrate my birthday
because being born
(Leonard:)was her achievement, not mine?
(Dr Gallo:)That's heartbreaking.
(Leonard:)Right? To this day,
I send her a card every year
(Leonard:)with a little money in it.
(Howard:)You know, once we get
the house back to ourselves,
(Howard:)we can be romantic
in any room we want.
(Bernadette:)Great. I can finally show you
where the laundry room is.
(Stuart:)Boy, who
would've thought
(Stuart:)when you asked me to move in
and help take care of your mom,
(Stuart:)I'd still be here
two years later?
(Bernadette:)Nobody thought that.
No one.
(Stuart:)Well, that's it.
(Bernadette:)I guess so.
(Stuart:)This is weird.
(chuckles)